gotwarcraft.com 2017-11-21

# About Us, Credits, and Policies - GotWarcraft.com

## So who is GotWarcraft?

Just a personal project. Started by the young’un and handed over to me.

You may have noticed that there are two distinct versions of this site. The old site has been around since WoW was in beta and is just a basic site. The new version is built around WordPress (this page, for example) and we’ve moved most all of the old stuff to the WordPress install. WP offers a lot of advantages, one of which is that anyone else writing for the site does not need to have DreamWeaver or some other website builder software.

**Interested in writing something for this site?** The contact info is below.

**Greg, aka RogPtor**

  * Head webdude in charge of everything on GotWarcraft
  * You can see us on Facebook, [here](http://www.facebook.com/GotWarcraft). Feel free to ask questions, make interesting comments, share anything posted there, point me to cool WoW related stuff, and so on.
  * My own FB homepage is [here](http://gregmee.com/).
  * On G+ the GotWarcraft page is [here](https://plus.google.com/u/0/b/103851901000614457348/103851901000614457348/posts) and my profile is [here](https://plus.google.com/111637678248700259872/posts).
  * We’re also [occasionally on Twitter](https://twitter.com/#%21/GotWarcraft)
  * I’m posting images from this site and elsewhere on [Pinterest](http://pinterest.com/gregmee/world-of-warcraft/). Feel free to follow any or all of my boards there.

and a couple of others who wish to remain nameless for now. If they ever decide to become more public then I’ll post their social sites here.

**Skip to:** Contact Us — Content — Privacy

## Contacting GW, the Form

You can reach us via…

  * comments on posts
  * The FB pages linked to above
  * The contact form in the toolbar at the bottom of the page (if you don’t see a toolbar then it might be blocked by one of your script blockers.
  * Or the form on [this page](http://gotwarcraft.com/contact.php).
  * No email address, due to excessive spam. Sorry, but the above should be more than adequate.

[contact-form subject=”Contact from Got Warcraft” to=”rogptor@gotwarcraft.com”] [contact-field label=”Name” type=”name” required=”true” /] [contact-field label=”Email” type=”email” required=”true” /] [contact-field label=”Website” type=”url” /] [contact-field label=”Comment” type=”textarea” required=”true” /] [/contact-form]

Feel to free to send comments, notes, suggestions, whatever. If you’d like to write something for us (and get links back to your page) then let us know.

## Content, Images, Etc.

You are welcome to use a portion of the content of any page as long as credit is given with a “do-follow” link back to the original page. Please do not copy the entire page or article.

The same applies to any of our images: feel free to use, but please provide a link back to the original page. You can find many of our images on [that pinning site](http://pinterest.com/gregmee/world-of-warcraft/). Feel free to comment, share, and repin if you’re there and something looks cool.

## Privacy Statement and Policies

**The Short Version**

This site pays the bills via affiliate sales (from Clickbank.com, Killerguides.com, Amazon.com, and others.) If you click through to a product you should assume that we will receive a commission if you buy that product.

GotWarcraft, like most sites, collects aggregate user info for generating statistics (such as visits per day.)

No personal info is collected unless you provide it directly (such as signing up for a newsletter, contacting us, or making a comment.) We do not collect any form of payment info. Any info received is for our use only and is not distributed elsewhere. We do not sell and information that we have collected.

Any site that we link to has it’s own set of policies and you should check those out, if so inclined.

**The Long Version**

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with GotWarcraft.com. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.

**Affiliate Relationships**

The pages (and links) on GotWarcraft.com generate income for the site owners based on affiliate relationships with various partners, including Amazon.com, merchants associated with Clickbank.com, KillerGuides.com, and possibly others.

Each of those merchants has their own set of privacy policies, which you will be able to find on their sites.

**Comment Policy**

On our blog comments are generally permitted. Any comments made, regardless of the content of the comment, are the words of the creator of the comment and do not necessarily reflect any views of GotWarcraft.com

All comments are subject to moderation and deletion without notice.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit GotWarcraft.com you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

Personal Information You Choose to Provide: When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

**Credit Card Information**

At this time GotWarcraft does not collect any of the following information beyond name and email (should you choose to join our newsletter.) Merchants that we link to will collect this information and they have their own policies and procedures. You can check those policies on their sites.

In the event the we ever do offer products or services for sale:

If you choose to avail of our services, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:

  * Name
  * Mailing address
  * Email address
  * Credit card number
  * Name on credit card
  * Credit card billing address
  * Business and home phone number

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

At this time GotWarcraft.com does not collect any personal information beyond the name and email of people who join our newsletter.

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you visit and browse our Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Sharing and Selling Information**

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address.

**What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out**

This site allows visitors to unsubscribe from our email services so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

**Acquisition or Changes in Ownership**

In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent

Back to Top

——————————————————————————–  
Last Updated: 4/16/12
